[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "When can we expect to see President Obama actually signing all this off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "We are expecting for him to sign that tonight.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Mr. President, do you believe this is going to happen all be over again in a few months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Is there any doubt really that there has been a big win for the White House tonight and a big defeat for the Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate", "House"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "-- Well, particularly inside the Republican leadership, not just in the Senate, but the House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Is he conceivable that he could emerge despite your misgivings just now as a potential nominee for Republicans, and could they win an election with somebody like him at the helm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Look, here is the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "EX", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "How long could we expect it to sit there before President Obama signs it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "If it is at the White House, it probably wouldn't sit there very long before he signs it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "Is this all bipartisan joy tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "We have got a lot of work we need to do together, and we have to work across the aisle to get it done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Obama Care"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Did the Republicans really, do you think feel that they have suffered a massive defeat here or is it a temporary setback?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe it was a worthy objective, Obama Care has significant issues and problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "And, congressman, which way did you vote tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NN", ",", "WDT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I voted with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "I presume that you voted in favor of it, as well, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Is it time, Josh Barro, that we considered actually bringing in some kind of severely punitive measure like that which focused all the politicians' minds in Washington?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I think a lot of that stuff ends up being kind of gimmicky.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh Barro"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$17 trillion"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Is it possible to avoid all of this when you have a $17 trillion national debt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "If you have grown-ups who will sit down and take a look at blue ribbon panel after blue ribbon panel of debt commission recommendations and everybody has to give something up and make hard choices and may be from that get re-elected, then you could solve the problem with the $17 trillion debt and deficits, and you can move forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$17 trillion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What are you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "IZZA: Well, this is a giant waste of time and makes you want to, you know, leave Washington and not cover politics anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Come on Ben Ferguson, what do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Hold on.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Can we get confirmation on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I am assuming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "And, Ben Ferguson, is Senator Cruz hero or villain in all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I think he is a brilliant guy that is going to end up being a hero absolutely coming out of this, because he has had all the attention, be focused now on two issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson", "Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Well, if you have a bigger gain plan is what happens next -- Ben Ferguson unless I'm misreading this, I would imagine come tomorrow and certainly all of next week what we'll see from Senator Ted Cruz is a rampaging of sort on Obama Care, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Obama Care"], "PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson", "Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 562, "question": "You think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I think the only --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Even Hillary Clinton?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Only people fainting at her at her rallies are going to be chubby gals from now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think she will be the Democrat nominee?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "I kind of hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Who would you next fear on the Democrat side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Who is the most electable right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "If he were the Republican candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Your vote makes it very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "I'm saying who do you think can exercise your desire to have a winner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I'm not sure, I want to see them in debates.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "But, my point is that do you think that he could be more electable to a wider cross section just to win the nomination and mind you, a Republicans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "We'll see, it is very possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "And Republicans don't do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last ten years"]}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Because that is all -- because there is no chapter more than ten pages, a lot of it is greatest hits of mine from the last ten years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "It is fun, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "It is fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Disagree with most of it, but I agree to some of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "No -- Do you actually write them yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I not only write them, I research it myself, which is why I don't have a T.V. or radio show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Do you like being so polarizing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131016pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "What do you hope to achieve with the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Well, my big goal was getting on this show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]